ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
You're so excited
about getting married to Changheng
that you can't fall asleep?
Don't forget that it's all fake.
Fake.
I don't care if it's fake or not.
I only marry the woman I like.
As for others,
I will not even look at them,
not to mention proposing a marriage.
Moon Supreme Lord.
Why didn't you even take a stand?
Moon Supreme Lord, wait.
Moon Supreme Lord.
At a time like this, can't you take care
of the overall situation?
What time is it?
Are you so eager to marry Xiao Run?
Wait. I should say Changheng.
I…
I'm trying to save both of their lives.
Besides, don't you also want
the plan to succeed?
My plan will not be built on marriage.
I'm not as casual as you are.
Who are you calling casual?
My lord.
Lady Wanqing is here.
She's outside right now.
Why is she here?
She said she has come to propose
to you.
Just in time.
That's right. Just in time.
I'll go tell her to give up the idea now.
No!
Moon Supreme Lord, I'm begging you.
Big Blockhead, stop there.
I'm telling you.
Go with me to see Lady Wanqing later.
And don't say a word.
How dare you command…
Not even one of you can make me relieved.
Sir, I've come to meet you.
There is no need for that here.
Hurry up. Please have a seat.
I'm sorry to bother you uninvited.
I wonder if you will blame me
for being rash?
Of course not.
We are more than happy
that you're here.
But sir, why won't you turn around
and look at me?
And why won't you say anything?
My brother is easily shy.
Lady Wanqing, have some tea.
That's right.
You're a gentleman.
I've been straightforward
about the reason for my visit.
I wonder what you think.
Will you dislike me
for being a mere street woman?
If you have any reluctance in your heart,
you must tell me.
How could he dislike you?
I should tell you.
Before you came,
my brother and I were also discussing
about proposing marriage to you.
I didn't expect you to come first.
Really?
Of course it's true.
Brother, why are you staring at me?
Didn't you just say you wanted
to marry Lady Wanqing
as my sister-in-law
with big dowry and eight palanquins?
Now that she's here,
why are you so shy?
Lady Wanqing. Look.
My brother is blushing.
I just wanted to tell you my feelings.
Even if I hadn't won your love,
I'd have no regrets.
It turns out
it's not just that I'm in love,
you have the same feelings too.
The savings I've made
over the past ten years
have all been used to pay for my life.
Although these three pieces of silk
are not worth big money,
they were weaved with my own hands
since I've met and missed you.
This would be my dowry.
They're as plain as snow.
Although I was a street girl,
I've never fallen.
I hope you'll accept them.
This is my birth date and horoscope.
Although there is no parental order
or matchmaker's agreement,
the rituals must be followed.
Sir.
Brother, take it.
I'll take it.
The birthdate should be
mutually exchanged.
I took the liberty of coming today.
You haven't written it yet.
I'm sorry I didn't think it through.
Tomorrow night,
I'll enjoy the moon in the lake.
If you finish it,
come and have a few drinks with me.
I asked you not to say anything
and you really didn't say a word.
You are quite cooperative.
Why are you glaring at me again?
Who said so aggressively he wanted
Lady Wanqing to give up the idea?
Why did you keep silent
while she was here?
Half-refusing, half-compromising.
You accused me of wanting to get married.
I think you also want to marry her.
I've been searching for him
all these days.
I never thought
the man of my dreams
would be your brother.
It's a great destiny.
Lady Orchid.
You look unhappy.
Do you have something on your mind?
No, nothing.
Of course I'm happy for you
seeing that you and your love
are getting married.
It's just…
Just what?
Lady Wanqing.
Actually, I…
I have a friend
who maybe, probably,
has fallen in love
with…
Love is love.
How can there be a maybe?
All right.
Then it's the case.
She has a crush on someone.
But she can't be with him
because of their status.
What do you think she should do?
Why do you ask this question, Lady Orchid?
I'm a woman from the Royal Academy.
In terms of status,
I am already the humblest.
But I wouldn't give up on the man I love
because of my status.
She doesn't have to worry about it,
Lady Orchid.
But the status I'm talking about
is much more fatal than yours.
If two families are deadly rivals
in which neither could tolerate the other,
but a person in this family…
But a person in this family
falls in love with someone
of the other family.
Now that a battle is around the corner,
they have to separate.
Then these two people must be
the biggest fools in the world.
Why?
If they give up their heart's desire
for something other than themselves,
what can they be but fools?
If it were an ordinary person,
it would be fine.
But the one she likes
has a great mission on his shoulders
that he can't give up.
What should they do then?
Do you mean yourself?
No.
Lady Wanqing.
Please answer me. Can you?
My answer remains the same.
How many people in this world
can meet their true love?
How many people can never meet
that person in their lifetime?
If they do,
they can't give up.
RIVER VILLAS
My lord.
It's already midnight.
Aren't you going to rest?
She said "also."
What does that mean?
When she left, she said,
"You accused me of wanting to get married.
I think you also want to marry her."
Does the word "also" mean
she really wants to marry Changheng?
My lord, you haven't said a word.
This is what you've been thinking about?
Why don't you ask Fairy Orchid?
I don't need to.
What does it matter to me
if she wants to marry or not?
Even if I do ask her,
what else can I do?
Shangque.
I'm here.
In your opinion,
how am I compared with Changheng?
How can Changheng be compared to you?
And my lord,
you've never asked such a question.
I've never really thought
that I would worry about not being able
to compete with others.
When Changheng was the God of War,
he was no match for me
in terms of strength,
strategy, and spirit.
Now that he has become a mortal,
he's even more stupid and dumb,
eating his head off.
Why does Orchid still want to marry him?
Do you think she's out of her mind?
That's not true.
She's not smart either.
She cares for Changheng
and protects him from anyone's bullying.
Even if he is now a mortal
with no power at all,
she still…
Am I
that inferior to Changheng?
Who do you really like?
Moon Supreme Lord or Lord Changheng?
Why are you asking this all of a sudden?
Tell me.
Can we not talk about this?
Haven't we had enough troubles lately?
Just tell me.
Are you really in love
with Moon Supreme Lord?
Do you want me
to send a message for you?
Don't talk nonsense.
Didn't I tell you already?
When I was still unformed,
I was already in love with Lord Changheng.
- What about now?
- Now…
I don't like Dongfang Qingcang anyway.
I'm not the kind of person
who constantly changes her mind.
What's wrong with a little change?
Mortals can only live for a few decades
and they change their mind.
We can both live 100,000 years.
If we stay the same
and always like the same person,
that would be boring.
What about you?
You were always pestering Shangque before.
Now all you talk about is Qu Shui.
Have you changed your mind
and like Qu Shui now?
That's nonsense. I don't like Qu Shui.
Then you must like Shangque.
They are both just my companions
for a good time.
I don't like either of them.
Anyway, I should tell you.
Qu Shui is only a man in this life.
After he succeeds in reincarnation,
he will become Fairy Danyin.
He'll be a female.
I know.
My lord.
Orchid has gone to sleep.
My lord, you've heard
everything she said just now?
Do you want me to repeat it?
I'm not deaf.
My lord,
you don't have to be so frustrated.
A girl often says things she doesn't mean
when facing the person she likes.
What she says and what she thinks
in her heart
may be completely opposite.
What do you mean?
I mean,
for example,
if she says she's not angry with you,
in fact, it means she is.
If she says it's nothing
and wants to be alone for a while,
then it means
she wants you to stay with her.
If she says she doesn't want a gift,
it means she does.
And if she says she doesn't like you,
actually it means
she may do.
There is this kind of thing?
So how can I tell
which statement is true and which is not?
Well…
A girl's mind
is the most difficult to guess.
Well…
I can't say.
This is so complicated
that even my lord is at a loss.
I see.
My lord, you and Orchid
are heart-connected, right?
It's just that
you're wearing the Jade Ring
and Orchid, the Heart-Hiding Hairpin,
so you can't read her mind.
If you take off the Jade Ring
and then replace Orchid's
Heart-Hiding Hairpin,
you'll know what she's thinking
without trying to guess.
Is what you said just now
a lie too?
What lie?
You said to Fairy Orchid
that you don't like me.
You mean this?
You said girls always say
what they don't mean.
Maybe it's not true that Fairy Orchid says
she doesn't like Moon Supreme Lord.
Then you said you don't like me.
Is it…
also a lie?
No.
I'm not like other girls.
I mean it
when I say I don't like you.
Why?
You wouldn't understand if I told you.
- I'm going to bed.
- Wait, Jieli.
You used to tease me all the time,
calling me stupid.
And you wouldn't talk to me seriously.
Then why don't you tell me today?
If you don't tell me,
how do you know I don't understand?
Actually, you're not stupid.
You're just too straightforward
and clean-hearted.
You're not like me.
What's the difference?
I think my heart and your heart
are the same.
I don't have a heart at all.
My heart and soul
were taken to a pawnshop
and sold for a living
when I was starving and freezing.
Who do I like or dislike?
To me,
feelings are just a passing flicker.
It's not worth believing in.
Then what do you believe in?
Money.
I only believe in money.
I just want to make money, be rich,
have my own big house,
big stores, and big business,
have branches across all three realms,
so that I can feel safe.
As for the rest,
I don't want to think about it.
I won't like anyone
in my life at all.
Do you understand?
I don't.
I knew you wouldn't understand.
Stupid Black Dragon.
Don't think about it.
Go to bed early.
Dongfang.
Why are you here so early in the morning?
It's a beautiful day,
a good time to go for a walk.
I'm going to take Lady Orchid
out for a walk
and spend some time with her.
I've already agreed to your marriage.
Why still spend time together?
Dongfang, you're wrong on this.
See? Although it's said
that brothers are like fathers,
the important matter of marriage needs
to be approved by Lady Orchid herself.
She knows very little about me.
I should at least let her
get to know me first.
- Absolutely…
- Lady Orchid.
Orchid, there are sugar cakes over there.
Do you want a sugar cake?
It's hot!
Why is it so hot?
Don't grab it with your hands from now on.
You can't even think of a way
not to get burned.
You're stupid indeed.
Forget it. I'm not hungry.
Flowers.
- There are flowers for sale there.
- Flowers.
Flowers.
Camellia in early spring.
Orchid. See which one you like.
Sir, please buy some flowers.
Turn around.
No need.
I don't like flowers.
That makes sense.
You're the best florist in Jinling.
These ordinary flowers
are not enough for you.
Why don't I take you on a boat trip?
I…
I'll miss you too.
Daqiang.
Bye.
Lady Orchid, are you all right?
My lord.
What's the state of mind
of Fairy Orchid at this moment?
Changheng is pursuing her like this.
Is she happy?
I don't know.
But last night, didn't you…
You didn't replace
the Heart-Hiding Hairpin?
No.
Orchid always says I'm superior,
high and mighty,
and don't understand her heart.
I don't believe
if I don't rely on One Heart Curse,
I won't understand what she's thinking.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Is there something I'm not doing well
that upsets you?
Orchid.
No.
Once upon a time,
I always looked forward
to spending all day with you,
listening to you talk,
and walking with you.
I dared not even think
how happy I would be
to have a day like today.
Once upon a time?
You've known me before?
I've known you for a long time.
I've known you
before you knew me.
I don't remember.
But when I was a child,
I went to Jinling with my father.
That was a long time ago.
It doesn't matter
if I don't remember the past.
What matters is the future.
I carried this jade in my birth coat.
People say
it represents
my future wealth and prosperity.
But I always feel
it doesn't belong to me.
I'm only keeping it temporarily.
It should belong
to the one I really love.
It wasn't until I met you
that I realized
you must be its owner.
Orchid, please take it.
And Lord Changheng praised me.
He said I'm a role model
for all fairies of Shuiyuntian.
He even gave me the Firefly Stone.
Think about it. What a coincidence?
Why did the fireflies fly
to my garden at Arbiter Hall
and nibble my flowers?
Does this mean
I'm destined to be with Lord Changheng?
You're unpredictable and unsteady.
Where is that coming from?
Every time she sees Changheng,
she's always smiling.
All she feels is sadness when I'm around.
That's right.
I always leave her alone
and be mean to her.
I always make her cry.
It's only natural
that she doesn't like me.
My lord.
I think…
Xiao Run, I'm sorry.
I should go now.
Excuse me.
Where is the gentleman who was here?
He seems to have gone over there.
Sir.
Big Blockhead.
Big Blockhead, I finally found you.
I have something to say to you.
Speak up.
I have an appointment.
What appointment?
Sir.
Lady Wanqing is already in the boat,
waiting for a long time.
Are you really going
to enjoy the moon with her?
Yes. What's wrong?
Didn't you say you wouldn't go?
I've changed my mind.
You're not going.
Why?
Because…
No reason.
Do I have to ask your permission
on whom I'm meeting with now?
Fairy Orchid.
The wedding dress?
Isn't this a woman's dress?
"Lady Orchid's wedding dress."
Qu Shui, you've got the wrong one.
Yes, I did.
I'll go to their house to change it.
I said I don't need your company.
It's just a few steps.
I'm just going to change
the wedding dress.
Why?
You're not happy now?
I know.
I shouldn't have bothered
your meeting with that Qu Shui.
Stupid Black Dragon.
Why can't you turn around?
Flower Festival is coming up in two days.
Once Lady Wanqing dies,
do you think Moon Supreme Lord
will let Xiao Run get away?
He'll definitely kill him too.
Then Qu Shui surely will not be able
to live either.
They're going to die anyway.
Let's go.
They're going to kill Xiao Run.
It's all a conspiracy.
I have to tell Xiao Run.
You dropped your stuff. Your stuff.
A conspiracy.
It's a conspiracy.
SHENSHUI HALL, SHUIYUNTIAN
Lord Changheng is going
through the tribulation.
It is better to return
the Magical Firefly Stone to him.
Even if it's a gift from Changheng,
you don't have to hold it
in your hand all day long.
I can't believe you remembered to return.
The moon is shining at this time.
Wouldn't it be better for you to drink
and enjoy the moon until dawn
with the beautiful lady?
I was just faking it.
You should be the one
who wants to enjoy the moon until dawn.
Why?
You're so excited about
getting married to Changheng
that you can't fall asleep?
That's a reminder.
I haven't tried on the wedding crown yet.
That's right.
I'm going to try on the wedding dress too.
Lady Orchid.
Help yourself.
You're the biggest idiot
in the three realms.
Fairy Danyin
let the immortal criminal
escape from Haotian Tower,
committing a serious crime.
According to the Immortal Law,
you'll be stripped of your immortal bone
and sent to Shenshui Hall,
staying in the mortal world forever.
Your Highness.
Danyin is young and reckless.
It's all because I didn't teach her well.
I'll suffer on behalf of her.
I hope that Your Highness…
Danyin.
Would you take the blame
and make a success of it?
At Your Highness's command.
Go back to Yunmeng Lake.
Kill the first God of War's
reincarnated body.
Destroy his spirit
and stop Dongfang Qingcang
from unlocking
the 100,000 Moon Tribe soldiers.
No way.
Nonsense! Don't be rude!
Please think twice, Your Highness.
Lord Changheng
is closely related to the fate
of the first God of War.
If you kill the first God of War…
If
Lord Changheng
thus also fails in his reincarnation,
he will be destroyed and scattered.
Changheng dared to escape
from Haotian Tower
and go to Shenshui Hall
to go through the reincarnation
to save the Moon Tribe spy,
repeatedly breaking the rules of heaven,
ignorant of heaven's rules.
Even if he comes back alive,
he'll still be a sinner of Shuiyuntian.
Thirty thousand years ago,
the first God of War also sealed
100,000 Moon Tribe soldiers with his life
for the peace in Shuiyuntian.
Since Changheng is the God of War,
he should take responsibility.
Your Highness,
please take back the order
and spare Lord Changheng's life.
I would rather
have my own immortal bone removed.
Your Highness is merciful.
Danyin
will not fail to fulfill her mission.
Now go.